<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">

    <!--
    These placeholder texts can be used to preview layouts with real content.
    The content in the English and German XML files is different on purpose.
    Some texts are localized (e.g. date) while others are just shorter in length.
    -->

    <string name="placeholder_event_title">
        Seidenstraße
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_subtitle">
        The Making of…
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_track">
        Art &amp; Beauty
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_abstract">
        Auf dem 30C3 wird es, neben der bisher gewohnten digitalen Infrastruktur mit
        Netz, Telefon etc. dieses Jahr auch erstmalig ein Rohrpost-System mit dem
        schönen Namen Seidenstraße geben. Als Inspiration dient die auf geschlossenen
        Drainagerohren und Staubsaugern basierende Installation OCTO der Künstlergruppe
        Telekommunisten, die einigen von der letzten transmediale bekannt sein dürfte.
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_description">
        Wir werden die Idee und Funktionsweise der Installation vorstellen, ihre
        Evolution von OCTO zur Seidenstraße als Offenes Kunstwerk, neue Features
        sowie von Entwicklung und Aufbau erzählen und vor allem, wie ihr mitmachen könnt!
        \n
        \nBesides the usual digital infrastructure with Wifi, telephone etc., 30C3 will
        feature for the first time a pneumatic tube system, with the pretty name
        Seidenstraße. The installation OCTO, built from drainage pipe and vacuum
        cleaners, by the artist group Telekommunisten served as inspiration – some
        of you might remember it from the last transmediale.
        \n
        \nWe will present the concept of the installation, its evolution from OCTO to
        Seidenstraße as an Open Artwork, new features, and talk about the setup,
        making of and of course, how to participate!
        \n
        \nProjektvorstellung und Mitmach-Agenda. Idee, Konzept, Realisierung, weitere
        Features etc.
        \n
        \nIn addition to this lecture, we are happy to announce that the Telekommunisten
        will also hold a workshop, where they will further explain concept and
        background of OCTO and open up the discussion for further input.
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_speakers">
        *m, Jeff Mann, frank, Diani Barreto
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_links">
        OCTO der Künstlergruppe Telekommunisten\nTelekommunisten workshop
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_online">
        https://events.ccc.de/congress/2013/Fahrplan/events/5610.html
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_language">
        de
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_day">
        Heute
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_start_time">
        11:45
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_duration">
        60 min.
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_room">
        Saal 2
    </string>

    <!-- Schedule time column -->
    <string name="placeholder_schedule_time">
        09:15
    </string>

    <!-- Alarm list -->

    <string name="placeholder_alarm_minutes">
        15
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_alarm_time">
        27.12.13 11:30 vorm.
    </string>

    <!-- Event detail bar -->

    <string name="placeholder_event_date">
        27.12.13 11:45 VORM. - SAAL 1
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_id">
        ID: 5610
    </string>

    <!-- Separators -->
    <string name="placeholder_day_separator_title">
        Tag 1
    </string>

</resources>
