<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">

    <!--
    These placeholder texts can be used to preview layouts with real content.
    The content in the English and German XML files is different on purpose.
    Some texts are localized (e.g. date) while others are just shorter in length.
    -->

    <string name="placeholder_event_title">
        Hardware Attacks, Advanced ARM Exploitation, and Android Hacking
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_subtitle">
        Discussion of recent research, live demonstration of techniques
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_track">
        Security &amp; Safety
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_abstract">
        In this talk (which in part was delivered at Infiltrate 2013 and NoSuchCon
        2013) we will discuss our recent research that is being rolled into our
        Practical ARM Exploitation course (sold out at Blackhat this year and last)
        on Linux and Android (for embedded applications and mobile devices). We
        will also demonstrate these techniques and discuss how we were able to
        discover them using several ARM hardware development platforms that we
        custom built.  Where relevant we will also discuss ARM exploitation as
        it related to Android as we wrote about in the "Android Hackers Handbook"
        which we co-authored and will be released in October 2013.
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_description">
        Lastly, we will also discuss some of our most recent related hardware
        research (to facilitate the above) which will include bus protocol
        eavesdropping/reverse engineering, demystifying hardware debugging, and
        surreptitiously obtaining embedded software (firmware) using hardware
        techniques. We will demonstrate and show the supportive tools used and
        techniques developed to perform this work and deploy them against Apple
        MFI iAP devices, and multimedia devices using OEM implemented USB stacks.
        (Which will briefly include our experiences around starting http://int3.cc
        where we sell a fully assembled modified version of a hardware USB fuzzer.)
        \n
        \nAlong the way we will inevitably share some of the lessons we also learned
        while completely designing the hardware (from scratch), writing the firmware,
        and mobile apps for an embedded security device called Osprey that we hold
        the patent for and have been publicly about publicly as a hardware vulnerability
        assessment swiss-army-knife for researchers.
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_speakers">
        Stephen A. Ridley
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_links">
        Don\'t Stuff Beans Up Your Nose\nINT3.CC\nThe Osprey (on INT3)
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_online">
        https://events.ccc.de/congress/2013/Fahrplan/events/5193.html
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_language">
        en
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_day">
        Today
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_start_time">
        17:15
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_duration">
        90 min.
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_room">
        REALLY LARGE ROOM
    </string>

    <!-- Schedule time column -->
    <string name="placeholder_schedule_time">
        09:15
    </string>

    <!-- Alarm list -->

    <string name="placeholder_alarm_minutes">
        5
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_alarm_time">
        12/28/13 5:10 PM
    </string>

    <!-- Event detail bar -->

    <string name="placeholder_event_date">
        12/28/13 5:15 PM - REALLY LARGE ROOM
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_id">
        ID: 5193
    </string>

    <!-- Separators -->
    <string name="placeholder_day_separator_title">
        Day 2
    </string>

</resources>
